In 2166 an immortal
tyrant named Vandal Savage
conquered the world and
murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan
is opposed by the body
I'd sworn my allegiance
to, the Time Masters.
In the future, my friends
may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered as legends.
Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
Two years. You left us stranded in 1958.
I was happy with the
life we built together,
the one I thought would be our future.
Chronos attacked us.
He sabotaged the ship and took Snart.
If you're gonna kill, you could
at least tell me what's going on.
The Time Masters,
they took me to a place
called the Vanishing Point.
I've spent lifetimes training
by them, being reborn.
Don't kill him.
The Time Masters took one of our own
and turned him against us.
I say we undo their handiwork.
I trust that you're comfortable, Mr. Rory.
Or do you answer to Chronos these days?
I don't take orders from you.
I can't believe I ever did.
Well, that's debatable.
I'm calling on you for two reasons.
First, we could use your help.
What's the second reason?
We're headed to 2147 to engage Savage.
Is that the second reason or the first?
Ah, forget it.
I owe you an apology, Mr. Rory.
I failed you.
I brought you along on this mission
under false pretenses, in
denial of your true nature.
And when that nature took its course,
I asked Mr. Snart to...
deal with you.
My point being,
your quarrel should be
with me and not with him.
Well, if it makes you feel any better,
I want to kill both of you.
Captain, we've arrived at 2147.
Thank you, Gideon.
Set a course for the Kasnian Conglomerate.
150 years in the future and
people are still wearing wool?
- Man, I hate wool.
- Be grateful, Mr. Jackson.
Those living outside
the Kasnian Conglomerate
are dressed in rags.
Conglomerate?
Yes, in the year 2080,
government began to
give way to corporations.
More like 2008.
According to Gideon, in two hours time,
our favorite immortal psychopath
is scheduled to attend a meeting
of the Conglomerate's share holders.
Ooh, sounds exciting.
You think Savage takes over
the world by trading stocks?
What we do know is, in 20 years time,
Kasnia is the foothold from which Savage
takes over the world, so we hardly want
to take him on there,
but if we can figure out
how his actions here
lead to his rise to power,
then we won't need to.
Copy that, Captain,
but if we're gonna be
checking out the future...
We should probably invite the nerd twins.
You know, I can already hear
what Stan's gonna say about 2147.
The future, it's...
- Fascinating.
- Astonishing.
Well, it was a 50-50 chance
which one he'd choose.
- Actually I was going to say, "Remarkable."
- Isn't it?
2147 was considered the world's zenith.
All of these people have five good years
to look forward to.
Before what?
Before a ruthless dictator
named Per Degaton comes to power,
releases the Armageddon Virus,
and most of them end up dead.
Well, that's depressing.
Whoa.
Is that my suit? That's my suit.
[woman screaming and people shouting]
- [laser zapping]
- Aah!
[suspenseful music]
You have been identified
as violating Ordinance 12.
That is how Per Degaton's father Tor
maintains order in Kasnia.
Doesn't look like progress to me.
Speaking of progress, we need
to get a better lay of the land.
And I need to get a better look at how
they made my suit autonomous.
Well, why don't you take
Martin and Jax with you?
Ms. Lance, Mr. Snart, and I
will work on locating Savage.
Tor Degaton holds daily meetings
with his board of directors.
And it's open to the public?
'Course not.
Just Kasnia's shareholders.
I hate to break it to you,
but we're not shareholders.
I'm more of a hard asset man, myself.
[tense music]
You're clear to attend.
They'll have to wait outside.
Oh, no, this is my accountant,
and she is my personal
assist... bodyguard.
Stockholders only.
[clears throat]
We've been through this.
I won't put the resolution to a vote.
Sir, with greatest respect,
the situation outside
the Conglomerate's borders
is becoming untenable.
The food riots, climate change.
I am well aware that the
world outside our walls
is descending into chaos,
but causing chaos cannot
be a proper response
It is not chaos.
It is logic.
The world's population is unsustainable
at current levels.
The herd must be thinned.
So you've argued, Mr. Savage,
but no matter how many times
you choose to press your point,
my decision shall stand.
Vandal.
Oh, my boy.
My father would have you
killed for calling me that.
Oh, I wouldn't want to chance execution.
Per Degaton.
So how did the meeting go?
Well, your father was being
his usual intractable self.
The problem is, my young student,
to run a corporation is not the same
as ruling a country.
If you're implying that my father
doesn't have what it takes...
Yes, he would have killed
me for that as well.
Well, I suppose I just have
to live dangerously then.
So how are your studies progressing?
♪ ♪
He's a teacher.
Tutor, it would seem, to
young Per Degaton himself.
You say that like it's
supposed to mean something.
After the death of his
father in five year's time,
Per Degaton unleashes
the Armageddon Virus,
which decimates the world's population,
leaving it ripe for conquest.
[both grunting]
Per Degaton primes the
world for dictatorship,
and then when the time is right...
Savage snatches that
power away from him.
By killing Per Degaton.
Indeed.
Okay, so we don't have what we need
to take out Savage, but
maybe now we can figure out
a way to stop his rise to power.
By depriving him of his
springboard, Per Degaton.
Okay, how do we do that?
It's quite simple, really.
We kill the little bastard ourselves.
[exciting music]
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
To be clear, we're talking
about murdering a child...
Who hasn't done anything to anyone...
Yet, so why don't we pick him off now,
while the picking's easy?
There's got to be a better way.
How do we even know that
this Per Degaton kid's path
to becoming a world-ruling
dictator is inevitable?
Because in the future that I'm from,
children learn about Per
Degaton in the same way
that children in your time
learn about Adolf Hitler.
What about addressing the
larger societal problems
that would allow such a
despot's rise to power?
We already know what pushes this punk
to the dark side: Savage.
Look, it's not the kid's fault
he's got an immortal
psychopath as his tutor.
If we don't kill the kid
now, Savage will as soon
as he's done using him
to take over the world.
If he doesn't build him
into the greatest tyrant
the world has ever known,
Savage can't become the last tyrant
the world will ever know.
Murdering a child in cold blood
just like Savage murdered your own son.
What's the use in saving the world
if we stoop to his methods to do so?
I'm with Professor Stein.
Okay, fine.
If y'all don't have the
guts to kill this kid...
Then removing him from the timeline
might be the next best thing.
Great, we've gone from infanticide
to child abduction. Progress.
First we need to devise how to abduct him
from underneath the noses of
his father's private guard.
And don't forget the army of Atom robots.
We're going to need an accomplished thief.
Well, while you're kidnapping baby Hitler,
Professor Stein and I will
sabotage the robot army.
I call Team Robot Army.
Isn't that a waste of time?
Not for the Kasnian citizens
who are tormented by my technology.
That technology does lead
to Savage's rise to power.
Good backup plan.
Fine, Team Kidnapping.
Go team.
[rousing music]
♪ ♪
Hey, you okay?
Yeah, yeah, I was just... thinking.
Ah, I think I understand.
You do?
Yeah, Savage.
He's so close you can sense him, right?
Yeah.
Do you want to talk about it?
No. Don't worry about me.
I'll be fine.
Okay.
Honey?
[upbeat jazzy music]
I'm home.
[door closes]
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Can I fix you a drink?
That would be lovely.
And while you do, you can
tell me what's on your mind.
Really, it's nothing.
You are a terrible liar.
Yes, but...
you love me anyway.
Beyond anything I can describe.
And because I love you, I know
when something's bothering you.
It's... it's just a feeling.
Of him?
It's hard to tell.
I haven't sensed Savage's presence,
but you do... or you think you do.
I think it's time for us to go.
I have some vacation time coming up.
We can drive to Coast City
and do some sightseeing.
A vacation isn't going to fix this.
I know.
Savage isn't just gonna forget
about us because we went away.
I know.
And he's not gonna stop until...
Mommy?
I can't sleep.
Hey, Slugger.
- Daddy.
- Come here.
[grunts]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
What's wrong?
Nothing. Nothing.
I just love you so much.
I love both of you so much.
[gasps]
♪ ♪
[tense music]
No litter. No street crime. No smog.
How soon can we leave?
Keep your eyes peeled.
According to Gideon, Per Degaton
should be passing through any minute
on his way to gymnastics class.
Are you telling me future Hitler
is enrolled in a gymnastics class?
Yes.
♪ ♪
I got eyes on Little Lord Fauntleroy.
I don't see him.
It's because he's surrounded
by Daddy's goon squad.
Northeast corner of the plaza.
Got him.
You sure you don't want to just shoot him?
It'd be a whole lot easier.
Stick to the plan, both of you.
Now, Ms. Lance.
[gunshot]
I'm in position.
It's up to you now, Mr. Snart.
♪ ♪
[lasers zapping]
[men exclaiming and shouting]
Since the introduction of our latest line
of autonomous law enforcement officers,
crime has dropped precipitously.
In fact, it's nonexistent.
Really?
Well, thank you for showing
us around, Dr. Brice.
It's my pleasure.
We don't get very many
visitors from Central City
ever since the S.T.A.R. Labs
Corporation took it over.
Uh, unless I'm mistaken,
your tech utilizes a dwarf star alloy.
The technology is proprietary, but yes.
How did you know, Doctor...
Lecter...
Dr. Hannibal Lecter.
So how did you get into
robotics, Dr. Brice?
Oh, well, it's in my blood.
Robotics have been a passion of my family
ever since my great-great-great-great
grandfather founded this company.
[dramatic music]
Is that...
Oh, my God.
♪ ♪
Huh, weird.
You look just like him.
Yes, I... I look just like...
yeah, that's... that's pretty weird.
I can't believe it.
I'm like the Werner Von Braun of robots.
The who?
The Nazi scientist who
invented the V2 rocket,
built it using slave labor,
then used it to level London.
Except my robots will one day be used
to level the entire world.
Ray, dude, do you not think
you're focusing on the wrong thing here?
I mean, you have a kid
you didn't even know about.
Had a kid. In this particular time period,
his offspring would be long since dead.
Thank you,
as if I wasn't already feeling bad enough.
How is it even possible that I'm someone's
great-great-great-great grandfather?
Before we left in 2016,
the only person I was...
Having sex with?
Ghosted me the week before we left.
Sh... she died?
No, no, ghosting.
It's where you pretend to be dead
by not answering somebody's text.
What a strange age for dating.
You think maybe she didn't
reply to your text because...
She knew she was pregnant?
[scoffs]
No wonder my kid started the company
that manufactures evil robots.
If I'd never left 2016,
my child would have had a loving father,
and Palmer Tech might not have gone on
to build a robot army that Savage uses
to conquer the world.
Bit of a stretch, don't you think?
Either way, I was someone's father
and didn't even know it.
- Hey.
Are you okay?
Fine. Oh, I'm fine.
You don't look fine.
I'm just a little... peckish.
Peckish?
It's nothing a little
energy bar won't fix.
I'll see you.
Edith and Joseph Boardman?
Our new names.
Joe Boardman is a good name.
And besides, I've never
kissed an Edith before,
but I certainly think
I can get used to that.
And what about all this?
How do we explain to our son
why his mother and father keep
moving every couple of years,
changing their names,
looking over their
shoulders at every turn?
I don't know why we thought
we could do this again.
Do you think we're selfish?
To have a family?
Because when Savage finds us...
- He won't.
- He always finds us.
Maybe this life is different.
Do you honestly believe that?
Look...
all I know is that Savage
is not the only thing
that's immortal, my love.
So is this.
What do genocidal maniacs
dream about, I wonder?
He's imagining himself baking
cookies with his mother.
Wait, you can monitor our dreams?
Of course. For example, last night,
you had a rollicking fantasy
involving a young nurse...
Okay, Gideon, enough.
Gideon, check the timeline to make sure
that the kidnapping of the boy
had the desired effect upon the future.
Oh, dear.
I'm afraid you'll be
disappointed with the results.
What do you mean, it did nothing?
I mean, that kidnapping Per Degaton
had a nominal effect upon the timeline.
Maybe we need to dump the little brat
somewhere he can't get into any trouble,
like the Stone Age.
No matter where and
when you sequester him
in the timeline, Savage
will still rise to power.
But Rip said this kid's
like a baby Hitler.
Yes, I also said that
time wants to happen,
and such a world-changing event
like Savage's rise to power
can't be stopped merely by
kidnapping his young pawn.
So we're back to plan A?
Snuffing the kid out in his sleep?
Let us not forget that
this kid will one day
be responsible for billions of deaths,
including those of my family.
Say that you do stop Savage
and save the lives of your family.
Will you be able to look
your own son in the eye
knowing what you did so he could live?
When the alternative is that
I shall never see him again.
I got a better idea.
Instead of us arguing about
whether we should kill him,
or where and when to dump him off,
why don't we just talk to him?
Savage has spent years
corrupting his mind.
It's not too late for
Per Degaton to change.
Says who?
Says someone with two tours
with the League of Assassins and a case
of bloodlust under her belt.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
[door opens]
Ah, finally,
someone who's willing to do a man's job.
Not why I'm here.
It's almost funny
how you guys keep parading in here
like it's some kind of
confessional or something.
It's also not why I'm here.
Okay, I'll bite.
Everybody's out there arguing about
whether or not we should kill this kid,
'cause no one thinks he can change,
which made me think of you.
You know no one thinks you can change.
That's why you're in here.
The only reason I'm in
here is if I get out,
I'm gonna give Snart some payback
he's not walking away from.
He saved your life.
He wussed out on killing
me, not the same thing.
He marooned me.
It's not like he had many choices.
You know, while you were busy
selling us out to a homicidal time pirate,
Leonard and I almost died.
He was thinking about you,
told me about your
partnership, your friendship.
Di it make you weepy?
You think it's gonna make me weepy?
He's your friend, a loyal one.
You should know that.
Well, thank you.
I'll work it out with
him as soon as I can.
Oh, killing a kid,
not very hero-like.
[beeping]
Mr. Degaton.
For the last 50 years,
everyone inside the Conglomerate
has submitted biosamples
so they can be tracked
and monitored at all times,
but these three...
Are not from the Conglomerate,
nor are they even from the last 50 years.
How do you know?
Long story.
What's important is that
I can get your son back.
How do you know they
haven't killed him already?
Because I know the
people who kidnapped him,
and they are weak...
squeamish in matters of death.
[tense music]
Who are you?
[laughs softly]
That's an excellent question.
[engine roars]
What was that?
That was our jump ship taking off.
How could Per Degaton have escaped?
Gideon, who else is on the jump ship?
It's being piloted by Captain Hunter.
Who just turned off his transponder.
Sounds like someone doesn't
want us following him.
Why?
Because Rip doesn't want us stopping him.
Stopping him from doing what?
From killing Per Degaton.
Okay, just think about this.
Where could Rip be taking Per Degaton?
Jump ship's got a range of
8,000 miles, so... anywhere.
It doesn't matter where he's taking him.
All that matters is
what he's gonna do to him
- when he gets there.
- Rip is not a murderer.
To Captain Hunter, this
isn't about a killing.
- It's about saving.
- Saving?
His son's life for Per Degaton's.
Rather simple if cold-blooded calculus
for a father to undertake.
[dramatic music]
Do you know who I am?
My father is going to...
Thank me?
I imagine there's a sizeable reward
for your safe return.
Relax.
You'll soon be home.
♪ ♪
Come on, honey, we got to get moving
or the train is going to leave without us.
Where are we going?
We are going on a little trip.
Just think of it as
one of your adventures.
The bad man found us,
the one that you and Mommy
talk about when I'm asleep?
Why is Vandal Savage chasing us?
It's time that he knew.
Come on.
Can you keep a secret, Aldus?
There's something... special
about your mommy and daddy.
We've known each other
for a very, very long time
and loved one another
since the day we met.
I already know that story.
[light laughter]
You know part of that story.
Have you ever heard of
a place called Egypt?
Well, it all began during
the rule of Ramses II,
when late one night a big, magical meteor
smashed into the Temple
of Horus, the hawk-god.
[footsteps tapping]
- Hey, you okay?
- Hey.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I was just thinking.
What are you thinking about?
Let me into that
4,000-year-old mind of yours.
The flashes I've been
having, they aren't of Savage.
They're of Carter.
- Oh.
- And they're not just memories.
They're feelings too.
Oh, well, I get that.
It must be really weird feeling like
you're cheating on me with him.
No, Ray.
I feel like I'm cheating on him with you.
I'm sorry.
No, it's... it's okay.
[chuckles]
I mean, I knew what I was getting into.
The last 206 times you fell in love,
it was with the same guy.
I guess this isn't a
great time to talk about
what's been bothering you.
Ah, uh...
You're not the only perceptive one.
So what's wrong?
Turns out that I had a
child I didn't know about
back in 2016, and here in the future,
my great-great-great-great granddaughter
creates the army of robot Gestapos
that Savage will one day
use to destroy the world.
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't want you to think less of me.
Ray, how could I ever think less of you?
Well, now that we've got
that off our chests...
What does that mean for us?
No luck finding our homicidal captain?
Gideon's still searching,
but I have a feeling
Rip's not gonna be found
if he doesn't want to be.
So what are you doing down here?
Don't you think you at
least owe him a conversation?
We had our conversation
while he was Chronos,
and he made his feelings
about me very clear.
And what about your feelings?
About you?
About Mick.
I don't have any feelings about Mick.
Look, it didn't seem that way
when we were dying in the
engine room of hypothermia.
Look, if you want to ease
your guilty conscience,
that's your business,
but he's still the same
son of a bitch he was
when you all wanted me to put him down.
I wasn't the one who
mentioned marooning Rory.
You did.
It's obviously still
weighing on your conscience.
So stop being an ass and go deal with it.
[tense music]
This isn't Kasnia.
I thought a neutral site
would be best for this.
For what?
Exchanging me?
Did your father ever teach
you to swim, Per Degaton?
No, I imagine he had someone
do it for him, didn't he?
You're hardly lacking
in tutors, are you...
such as Mr. Savage.
What are you talking about?
My son Jonas always
wanted to learn to swim.
I promised him that I'd teach him,
but there never seemed to be... time.
My son never learned to swim,
because he was killed.
So... you brought me here to kill me.
I brought you here to save my son's life,
your life in exchange for his.
♪ ♪
I'm sorry.
No you're not.
You're not sorry,
because you're not going to kill me.
I have to.
To save my wife and son, I have to.
I don't expect you to understand.
It doesn't matter if I understand.
I can see it in your eyes.
You're not going to do it.
You're like my father, weak.
[gun clicks, charges]
Vandal Savage has taught me many things,
including what a killer looks like.
You're not a killer.
Your tutor has taught you well,
despite his ill intentions.
Vandal loves me.
Oh, he wants to use you as his pawn,
and ultimately, he will betray you.
No. No, he wouldn't.
I've said to myself time and time again
that there is nothing that I wouldn't do
to save my wife and son,
but now I know that there is.
My reticence to kill you, Per Degaton,
is not weakness.
It is goodness.
And if there is a shred
of goodness inside of me,
then I have to believe
that there is a shred
of goodness inside of you.
Be the man that your
father wants you to be,
not the man Savage wants you to be.
[stirring music]
Savage, he's coming.
[loud blast]
Gideon?
Tor Degaton's forces
have surrounded the ship.
[lasers zapping]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
I'm afraid our shields
will not be able to sustain
continued bombardment.
You're afraid?
Here's an idea: why don't you fire back?
I would, except...
The flying robots already
targeted our weapons systems.
We don't need weapons.
He's right. We have super powers.
[dramatic music]
[all grunting]
I think this is yours.
[both exclaim]
♪ ♪
[lasers zapping]
I'll draw their fire. You
handle the ground troops.
Aah!
Ugh!
Ray, are you all right?
So this is what it feels
like to be last year's model.
They're too fast. We
have to find another way.
Forget about them. We'll
hold off the robots.
We'll take out their command center.
Who are you?
Yeah.
Ray, hurry up.
I can only hold them back for so long.
Where did you get your suit?
Look, if you don't let us disable
your evil robot army,
then the whole world will be destroyed.
They're designed to bring peace.
I know.
I designed the robots.
What?
I am your great-great-great-great
grandfather, the guy you have a bust of
in your lobby, father
of the robotics industry.
You're trying to tell me
that you're Sidney Palmer?
Sidney?
Wait, the bust in your lobby
is of my stupid brother?
Of course.
He must have gone to work for Felicity
in 2016 after I vanished.
He allowed my tech to be perverted
by the defense industry.
That is so Sidney.
So that means that she's not...
I'm not a father.
So we still need your
help disabling the robots.
A... and why should I believe you?
Because if you have even
a drop of Palmer blood
in your veins, you'll do what's right.
[lasers zapping]
Looks like Raymond was able
to sabotage his robot army.
Which means mopping up
the rest of these guys
shouldn't be a problem.
Oh, it will be a problem.
What do you want?
I want to exchange this woman's life
for your captain, Rip Hunter.
I have a better idea:
her life in exchange for his.
Your son will be returned to you
as soon as you guarantee our safe passage.
Don't do it, Father.
If you let them go now,
they will only come back
for us in the future.
It's your choice.
[gun clicks, charges]
Your son is right.
We should kill them all.
Put down your weapons!
- No, Father.
- Let my son go,
and I will let you leave in peace.
You have my word.
[tense music]
Better find yourself a new mentor, kid.
What do you want?
People seem to think we
should have a heart-to-heart.
We don't have hearts.
Where does that leave us?
I've got a dozen reasons for killing you.
You've got a dozen and
one for killing me, so...
All the talk in the world
is not gonna change a thing.
Exactly, here's my proposal.
I open this cell, we let
our fists do the talking.
When I kill you...
You take the jump ship, make your escape,
live out the rest of your
life anywhere you like.
Hmm.
And if you kill me, well,
it's better than being
locked up in this place
like some kind of circus freak.
I take that as a yes.
Sound the bell.
Hey.
You don't have to knock.
- It's your room too.
- Yeah, I know.
It's just... things have been weird.
Since I told you I had a love child
that I didn't really have,
or since you told me that
you're still in love with...
You know what I love about you, Ray, is,
you always manage to find the bright side.
And no matter what, you never give up.
So please, don't give up on us.
I'm not giving up,
but it's hard to ignore the math.
You and Carter have
spent lifetimes together,
and in each one, you've fallen in love,
so why would this
lifetime be any different?
Well, I never met you before.
Look, Ray, Carter is my past.
You are my future.
Vandal.
Oh, I didn't expect you
up and about so soon.
My father wanted me to rest,
but I wanted to resume my studies.
Oh, good boy.
So... where should we begin?
Well, I was thinking Greek mythology.
Do you know the tale of Oedipus Rex?
He was a prince of thieves
before his father exiled him.
Why?
Well, because the king was a coward.
He had heard a prophecy
that one day his son
would take his crown, so
he bound his boy's feet
and tossed him into the woods to die.
What did the boy do?
He did what he had to do.
And one day, the prophecy came true,
and the prince became a
great and powerful king.
Though it wasn't easy.
Great things are never easy.
[dark music]
Unfortunately, our
interactions have done nothing
to halt Per Degaton's rise to power.
If anything, we've merely cemented it.
In fact, the virus, which
wasn't supposed to be
unleashed upon the world
for another five years...
I'm sorry, Father.
Will now be released in a matter of days.
As you all know, our
former chairman's chair
is in the Conglomerate passed to his son,
who due to his age elected
me to act as his proxy.
First order of business,
I would like to revisit our discussion
concerning the population crisis
beyond the Conglomerate's borders.
As we all know, we
already have a solution.
Did I do the right thing, Gideon?
Not committing murder
is generally considered
the right thing, Captain.
In this instance...
I wonder.
[both grunting]
We had a deal, Mick.
Kill me and you walk.
It's what you wanted, isn't it,
to get off the team?
I don't know what I want anymore.
Truth is, it doesn't matter.
What are you talking about?
Whether I stay or leave, I'm dead.
We're all dead.
Since I failed to bring you in,
the Time Master's want to bring me in,
and this time, they're not
gonna take any chances.
They're called the Hunters, mercenaries,
and unlike me, there isn't
a human part left in them.
So they want to lock us all
up in the Vanishing Point?
The Hunters do one thing:
kill,
whenever, wherever,
and they'll stop at nothing
till every single one of us
is erased from the face of history.
Do you have any suggestions
as to how we might
outsmart them, Mr. Rory?
Run.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -