In 2166, an immortal
tyrant named Vandal Savage
conquered the world and
murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan
is opposed by the body
I'd sworn my allegiance
to, the Time Masters.
In the future, my
friends may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered as legends.
Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
Sorry we're late.
Aren't you even a little bit
happy to be back on the ship?
I was happy with that
life we built together.
You think I was hunting
you and your friends
because the Time Masters made me?
They barely had to ask.
Since I failed to bring you in,
the Time Masters want to bring me in.
They're called the Hunters,
and they'll stop at nothing
till every single one of us is
erased from the face of history.
- Do you have any suggestions?
- Run.
[ship engines roar]
_
Aah! It's been quite a
while since I time-jumped
far enough to experience side effects.
Fond memories.
- I can't feel my face.
- Fine feel I.
Linguistic dysplasia,
that should pass shortly.
Better it now.
Am I the only one who
can't feel their face?
I can't feel my... I better not say.
Mr. Rory appears unaffected.
What's going on? We time-jump?
Yeah, we time-jumped.
But "where to?" is the better question.
The town of Salvation,
the Dakota territory, 1871.
I can't believe it... the Old West.
- This isn't going to work.
- It'll buy us time.
We can hide out here while the Hunters
search the other Fragmentations.
What if they decide to
check this place first?
You know, feel free to loop
us in whenever it's convenient.
As you've seen, time doesn't
operate as is generally thought.
It wants to happen. It
takes time to harden.
The... the timeline is unclear on occasion,
constantly in flux.
Hence the difficulty in locating
Savage throughout history.
Indeed. And one of the
other interesting notions
of time travel is the
existence of Fragmentations.
Temporal blind spots,
specific places and times
the Time Masters can't see.
The town of Salvation and
its surrounding environs
are located within one
of these Fragmentations.
So, basically, we're
hiding out in the Old West
and hoping your boogeymen
don't find us here.
The Hunters are not boogeymen.
And you better hope they don't find us.
Well, at least not until I get a chance
to "punch a few doggies"
or "bust a bronco" or two.
Not that I condone animal cruelty.
It's just that I watched
a lot of Westerns as a kid.
Alas, you'll have to enjoy
the Old West from in here,
I'm afraid.
Oh, come on.
What's the harm in us
just taking a look around?
With this group?
Clearly, you haven't been paying attention.
Ugh, if I'm in the Old West
and I don't get to look around,
I'm going to kick myself.
I could help with that.
I'll keep an eye on them. Don't worry.
I'll be a good boy.
[lasers squeal]
[chuckles] I look just like Wyatt Earp.
Now, the fabricator can make clothing,
but you're also going to need
era-appropriate protection.
This era can get a little, uh, rough.
- Oh, six shooters?
- Actually, most guns
of that time period had hammer blocks,
thus reducing the number of shots to five.
Now, this should go without saying,
but considering this group,
I am going to say it...
only use these weapons in the
case of extreme emergencies.
You make it sound like
you're not coming with.
From your duster and
revolver, I'd imagined you
as much an Old West
aficionado as Dr. Palmer.
Indeed I am. But my time
is best spent back here
on the ship, plotting our next
move against Vandal Savage.
Besides, as Mr. Rory says,
it's only a matter of time
before the Hunters find us here.
Don't worry. We're not
going to put down roots.
Yeah, we'll stay out of trouble.
Mm, how I hope and pray that to be true.
[dramatic Western music]
♪ ♪
Yahoo!
[indistinct chatter]
[saloon piano music]
Remember, we're just here
to get the lay of the land.
- No trouble.
- Sure that'll happen.
I need a drink.
Wow. It's a real old-timey saloon.
Oh, I beg your pardon.
Not at all, ma'am.
♪ ♪
That tastes like gasoline.
Pretty much. Hit me again.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
It's no bother.
Time doesn't pass normally
in the Vanishing Point.
It's been years since I've
seen the bottom of a glass.
Years?
How long were you...
Chronos?
Never counted. Doesn't matter.
Turns out it was just another gig anyway.
Doesn't seem like it.
You're different now.
Better or worse?
Don't know yet.
You can handle your liquor. I like that.
I've been on more than a few
dates with guys who thought
we'd get wasted and they'd get lucky,
but somehow they always ended
up the ones under the table.
Mm.
You haven't drunk with me.
Is that a challenge, Mick?
Line them up.
Didn't know you played cards.
Like you, Mr. Snart, I am an enigma.
Raise.
Aha.
- Thank you, gentlemen.
- I'm impressed.
My father was what some might call
a degenerate gambler,
others would say criminal.
When I was old enough, he'd pull
me in on some of his schemes.
I picked up a thing or two at a few
of the card tables he frequented.
Then I took
a different path.
Like father, like son isn't
always inevitable, Mr. Snart.
- I had a full boat.
- As did I.
Full of kings, which
beats your pair of queens.
Don't I look busy to you?
I'm sorry. I...
You spill another drop of
that whiskey, and you will be.
Just because you're losing doesn't
mean you have to pick on the waitstaff.
Mind your own business, grandpa.
Unhand the lady.
Now, now, boys, let's just take it easy.
Oh, when my friend here
is being reasonable,
we know we have a problem.
I'm not the one with the problem.
You are.
[gunshot, patrons gasp, scream]
[body thumps]
You killed him.
You're welcome.
Clearly, the deceased
was a friend of yours,
but my friend here...
Your friend drew first,
got put down.
It was a clean shot.
Do we look like we care about clean?
He has a point.
[upbeat saloon music]
♪ ♪
[glass shattering]
[music stops]
[gunshot]
All right!
Playtime's over.
Anybody's got a problem with that,
they answer to me.
Thank you,
Mister...
Hex.
Jonah Hex.
You're not from around here, are you?
No.
My friends and I are, uh...
from out of town.
Way out of town.
All right.
Why don't you folks tell
me where you're really from?
I'm not sure that's any
of your business, sir.
Let me rephrase that.
Tell me when y'all from.
You seven stick out like a dog in a manger.
Like he said, we're not from around here.
You think you're the first time
travelers I've ever come across?
Uh, yes.
Where is he?
I got some words that need saying.
Where is who?
Rip Hunter.
[tapping]
What is it about you people that
whenever we go to a new timeline,
you feel the need to pick up...
strays?
Nice.
I didn't get to see it last time around.
Last time?
A long story, which we will not be telling.
My coat suits you good.
What are you doing here, Jonah?
Collecting on a bounty,
wetting my whistle,
when your friends here
got in a lot of trouble.
We might've gotten into a
barroom brawl back in town.
Well, that was entirely predictable.
One of them poured lead into a
member of the Stillwater gang.
- Mr. Rory.
- Snart, actually.
Oh, that was gonna be my next guess.
This guy tried to kill Grey.
Snart saved him.
And brought this town a whole
lot of hell in the bargain.
Those boys you were trading
hands with in the saloon...
they're all members of the Stillwater gang.
Why can't a gang ever
be a bunch of good guys?
Jeb Stillwater and his friends
been raiding this town
for the past three months.
Stealing, robbing, killing.
Well, he'll have to go through us.
No, he won't.
No doubt your... your little ruckus
has already placed the timeline at risk,
to say nothing of potentially
alerting the Hunters
to our presence here.
Sounds like someone's planning
on busting out of town again.
Leaving already?
No. No.
Look, this town is being
terrorized by the Stillwater gang.
And I aim to do something about it.
You "aim to"?
You getting all native on us, Haircut?
Look, we signed on to this mission...
To stop Vandal Savage.
To be heroes.
And saving a town from a
marauding gang of criminals...
that is what heroes do.
[chuckles]
Quite a posse of saints you're
riding along with nowadays.
Hey. Bridge is, uh, that way.
Yeah, I'm not going to
the bridge. I'm, uh...
Where am I going, Gideon?
The valley you described is
consistent with Albano Gulch.
Yeah, there.
Okay, wait. Why?
[sighs] Back at the
saloon, I ran into a woman,
and she caused me to have
more memory flashes, so...
I think I might have known
her in one of my past lives.
And if so, she might be
able to help me find Carter.
Wait. So you're just gonna run
out there and try and find her?
Actually, I was planning on flying.
You want a partner in crime?
Okay, fine.
But you're definitely not carrying me.
How do you propose we get there?
[Western music]
♪ ♪
[clears throat]
Howdy.
I'm Ray... John Wayne.
What do you want, Mr. Wayne?
Well, I, uh... I reckon you could use
another hand with the Stillwater gang.
You boys have any experience
with law enforcement?
Well, I have a fair bit of
experience fighting crime.
Congratulations, then.
♪ ♪
You're making me your deputy?
Nope. Just made you the new sheriff.
- Excuse me. What?
- Stillwater gang
has been shooting up
this town for months now.
It's only by the grace of the good Lord
that I'm not pushing up daisies myself.
And I am done with pushing my luck.
But you're the...
sheriff.
Congratulations.
By the way,
you might find a warrant or two
out for me around these parts.
You know, we have stuff back on the
ship that can fix your... you know...
Fix what?
Yep. Nothing. Never mind.
[hooves clomping]
[saloon music]
♪ ♪
What can I get you?
Information.
Some friends of mine are
looking for Jeb Stillwater.
If they're the same friends
that shot Billy Conlon
and beat on the Stillwater posse,
I can guarantee you he'll find you.
That being said, we'd very
much like to find him first.
You got any more of them greenbacks?
Let me go find a map.
[sniffling, sighs]
Excuse me, ma'am. Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I just want to be alone.
I understand.
I'm new to these parts.
I didn't think it was customary
for a lady to drink alone.
Tonic water.
It's for my son.
I just needed a moment to myself.
Is everything all right?
I should be getting back to my boy.
If there's something wrong with
him, perhaps I can be of assistance.
I happen to be a scientist.
That's kind.
But I'm afraid there's nothing you can do.
My boy is going to die.
What's wrong with him?
He has the consumption, they say.
Tuberculosis.
He's been like this on and
off for about a year now.
He always wanted to see the American West.
Our doctor thought a constitutional
might do him some good.
It hasn't, clearly.
You know, there are medicines that...
The doctor here says he has a day...
maybe two, if he's lucky.
Does he look lucky to you, Mister...
I don't know your name.
It's Martin.
Hello, young man.
We call him Bertie.
Bertie.
Your mother tells me you
wanted to come out west.
Can't imagine you've seen much of it yet.
I want to ride a stagecoach.
Well, in that case...
I encourage you to get better.
My mum... she's not sure I will.
[shudders]
Well, then you must
prove your mother wrong...
so you can ride that stagecoach.
[gunshots, shouting outside]
[gunshots]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
One of mine is dead.
And this here town's gonna pay.
♪ ♪
Now, who the hell are you supposed to be?
John Wayne...
Salvation's new sheriff.
And this here town is under my protection.
Well, you being new and all,
you don't know about the
arrangement that we got.
See, me and my boys, we ride into town,
we take whatever we want.
In exchange for what?
- Not killing nobody.
- [light laughter]
Well, that sounds reasonable and all,
but arrangement's over.
- Arrangement's over, boys.
- [light laughter]
They teach you numbers
where it is you're from?
'Cause the way I see it,
there's only one of you
and a whole mess of us.
[gunshot, horse neighs]
You get out of town,
and you don't come back,
or the next bullet goes in your eye.
I got sharpshooters all around.
You really want to test me?
[dramatic music]
Let's ride, boys.
♪ ♪
Hyah!
[men shouting]
[cheers and applause]
Nice, Haircut.
[chuckles] Dude, that was badass.
Let's not oversell it.
Running a bad guy out of town's always been
- on my bucket list.
- "Bucket list"?
A list of things one hopes
to accomplish before they die.
Well, you better hope it's a
real short list, String Bean.
We can handle the Stillwater gang.
Well, you're all just tearing
up the 1870s, aren't you?
Stillwater and his gang's
like a hornets' nest,
and your friends here keep poking at it.
They saved the town from being raided, man.
Today, but what about tomorrow...
or the day after that?
For a bunch of time travelers,
you don't seem to
understand the future much.
The day will come when you'll all leave...
and Salvation will end up like Calvert.
What's a Calvert?
A closed matter.
A word, Mr. Hex?
I believe you've all
done enough for one day.
Well, now I definitely want
to know what a Calvert is.
Then it's a good thing we have
access to a supercomputer. Gideon?
Calvert was a town in Oklahoma circa 1868.
"Was"?
[beeping]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[bird screeches]
You know, there's something
weird going on with your face.
What?
- You're smiling.
- [chuckles]
I didn't know you could do that.
Well, don't tell anyone my secret.
[laughs]
It's just all of this...
it's so pure, so simple.
I'd say I miss simple,
but I guess you have to experience
something first to miss it.
I know what you mean.
I've been having more and
more memory flashes lately,
and I'm not entirely sure why.
Well, if this woman was a
friend of yours in a past life,
hopefully she'll have
another piece for your puzzle.
I feel like I'm being drawn to this place.
Which way?
There.
[smacks lips]
You know, stealing's against the law.
I'm the sheriff of these here parts.
How did you know I was
appropriating this medicine?
That was my fault, Professor.
Et tu, Gideon?
I suppose this is going
to earn me a lecture
on the perils of upsetting the timeline
by introducing futuristic
medicine to the 19th century.
Well, it seems you've
already given it to yourself.
Except this isn't futuristic medicine.
I've had Gideon fabricate
simple streptomycin for me.
Excuse me.
Which won't be used in medical
treatments for another 70 years.
This is about a boy in town who's
dying of an easily curable disease.
Just as you couldn't turn
your back on Jeb Stillwater
and his gang, I can't turn
mine on this boy and his mother.
Except Dr. Palmer is using
19th-century technology
to deal with Stillwater, whereas you...
Just spare me the lecture, Captain Hunter.
You, of all people...
This isn't about the mission, Martin!
Do you not recall happened when Dr. Palmer
left a bit of his suit back in 1975
and nearly destroyed Central City?
That was an accident.
I'm not talking about our mission
or Dr. Palmer's technological gaffe.
Calvert...
that town clearly holds some
emotional resonance for you,
judging from the looks you've
been exchanging with Mr. Hex.
How do you know it's a town?
Gideon?
Calvert, Oklahoma...
what happened to you there, Rip?
And why is it so important to you?
Because the past is prologue.
It's not uncommon for criminal posses
such as Mr. Stillwater's
to sack and pillage towns
which they find uncooperative.
So Stillwater's done this before?
In the case of Calvert, it
was Quentin Turnbull's doing.
But it was my fault.
I'd come to Calvert on a
mission from the Time Masters.
This was years before
my son Jonas was born.
Jonas...
Did you name your son after Hex?
After my mission was completed,
I felt unable to leave.
I'd grown so attached to this era...
a victim of the same time
drift you experienced in 1958.
But obviously you left at some point.
Left? I had to tear myself
away from the time period
for fear that I would never see
my then-future wife, Miranda,
ever again.
Turnbull attacked
Calvert the very next day.
So...
you can understand why I must act.
No, Martin, I don't.
As I said before, this is advanced
medicine unsuitable to the period,
to say nothing of what this boy's
survival might do to the timeline.
Be that as it may,
I refuse to live with the regret
I see on your face right now.
The information Mr. Stein
got from the barkeep paid out.
I know where the
Stillwater gang's holed up.
All right. Let's ride.
Up high.
You coming, Rip?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
That's what I thought.
[beeping]
[door whirs closed]
I wonder why she lives
alone all the way out here.
Because...
I value my privacy!
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't you remember me...
from the saloon back in Salvation?
I remembered you, you
wigged-out little girl.
If I'd wanted to talk to you then,
I would have talked to you then.
I ain't fixing to talk to you now.
Now, get off of my land!
Listen, we're not trying
to start any trouble.
Do you want that pretty little
mouth of yours filled with lead?
Your friend has a colorful personality.
I ain't got friends. I keep to myself.
She's right.
She wasn't my friend.
I was her.
We sat for that picture
at the county fair, 1830.
He looked like such a gentleman.
What was his name?
Hannibal.
Hannibal Hawkes.
And what happened?
Was it Savage?
What is this?
It looks familiar.
That was ours in our first life.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I remember.
We crossed with Savage in Jefferson City.
He had it with him.
We escaped with it and our lives.
Do you still have it?
We lost it to bandits about a year later.
We heard that the Pinkertons
were after the same bandits,
but we just...
Hey. What is it?
Objects present at the moment of my...
our first death
can be used to kill Savage.
So, if I can get my hands
on that bracelet, then...
You're going to try to
kill Savage with a bracelet?
You need to stop.
- Stop what?
- Fighting our destiny.
Ain't destiny what brought you here?
What part of destiny is she fighting?
All of it.
We get reborn. We find
Hannibal... Carter...
then Savage finds us, and then we die.
That's... that's the way it is.
It's the way it's always gonna be.
I don't believe that.
Well, I have a few more years on you.
You can't break the cycle.
That's why I live out here, alone.
For the rest of your life?
Well, I guess I had to
figure that out the hard way.
I was still a young woman
when Savage left me a widow.
Instead of waiting for
him to find me and kill me
so that I could love my
Hannibal in the next life,
I tried to find love in this one.
Talk about a curse.
What happened?
He was a good man, but
he wasn't a soul mate.
It was like fate was
trying to break us apart.
Eventually, fate broke both our hearts.
So I made a promise to myself
that I wasn't gonna do
that to a person again.
I'm... I'm sorry to hear that.
No, I'm who's sorry...
to have to be the one to let you know
that you're never going to be
able to love anyone else, ever.
How much do you know
about our previous lives?
I reckon not a lot because
you didn't recognize me,
so let me tell you that
we did love other men...
loved them real and pure,
but it never ended well, not ever.
Tragedy or heartbreak...
that's how it always ends
if the man's not Carter.
We could've used Sara on this roundup.
A lady? You crazy?
Just remember, we're here to
arrest Stillwater, not kill him.
He always this much of a stick in the mud?
Yes.
How? It's a miracle.
Oh, it's... it's not a
miracle, I can assure you.
Uh, M-Mrs. Neal...
Sarah.
Sarah...
when the illness is gone,
I need you to promise me
that you'll take what's left
of the medicine and burn it,
vials and all. Do you understand?
Yes. Yes, I shall do it.
Sarah...
I wish you well.
Thank you.
I really must be going.
[door opens, closes]
[horse neighs in the
distance, hooves clomping]
Oh, damn.
[grunts]
[gunshots]
These boys got some stones.
[gunshot]
[snarls]
[rousing music]
♪ ♪
Jeb Stillwater, you are under arrest.
You have the right to remain silent.
You have the right to an attorney.
There won't be Miranda
rights for another 100 years.
Fall back! Fall back!
Jax!
[guns click]
- We got to go!
- Not without Jax!
Well, we got Stillwater.
It means we got leverage.
Live to fight another day or die tonight...
your choice.
Hyah!
♪ ♪
Where is Stillwater?
He's knocked out cold in the med bay.
Well, this is a simple matter.
We trade Stillwater for
Jefferson as Mr. Hex suggested.
It's not that simple.
If we release Stillwater,
we're back to square one
and the town is still in danger.
So is the kid.
And we'll figure out a way to get
him back without releasing Stillwater.
I got a notion.
Set up a quick draw.
You win,
get your guy back.
You lose,
you set Stillwater free.
And, by "lose," you mean...
Get shot and killed.
Oh, great. Pistols at high noon.
Finally, someone's talking sense.
There has to be another way, a better way.
Sure.
Go after Stillwater with all
your gear from the future.
I don't know how that'll sit
with your captain, though.
Mm, let's assume it's a bad idea.
So who's standing in the
middle of Main Street?
I'll do it.
Raymond, now is not the time to
indulge your cowboy fantasies.
No one else is stepping forward.
Plus, I'm a decent shot...
at least I was with an air rifle.
I can't believe you're encouraging this.
You know it's the only way.
Dr. Palmer's going to get himself killed.
I think you forfeited
your right to an opinion
when you refused to leave the
ship since we've been here.
I had good reason.
Because of Calvert.
Yes, but not in the way you think.
Leaving Calvert, leaving this... era
is one of the hardest
things I've ever had to do.
And why is that, Captain?
A Time Master is trained to do
his work without interference,
which means not helping
people or being a hero.
But as you've seen, Dr. Palmer, this era
offers many opportunities for heroism.
I found it...
enticing.
And you still managed to leave.
Something's been bugging
me all these years.
If you'd have known what
Turnbull was going to do
to Calvert, would you have left?
That's the thing, Jonah.
I did know.
[grunts]
[groans]
I deserve that.
You deserve a lot worse.
You knew, and you still left?
Of course I knew. I was a Time Master.
And therein lay the problem.
Like Raymond, like Martin,
I felt the pull of heroism,
of this era's penchant
for being rife with opportunities
to make a difference.
That's one of the things that called to me,
and that is why I had to leave.
Because had I stayed...
I could no longer have
remained a Time Master.
But I'm no longer a Time Master...
which is why I'll face Stillwater.
Wait. I said that I would do it.
And get yourself shot and killed?
It's appreciated, but I'd
rather you stayed alive.
Send word to Stillwater's posse.
I believe high noon is
in less than three hours.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
You want to talk about it?
Not really.
You don't have to listen to her, you know?
Is this you not talking about it?
No. This is me ignoring you saying
you don't want to talk about it.
Look, I get it.
Things may have gone very
wrong for Old West you
and whoever she loved who wasn't Carter.
But?
But Old West you didn't know Ray Palmer.
She didn't love Ray Palmer.
You do.
And you have to live your life.
She already lived hers.
You think Hunter can pull this off?
Reasonably.
If not, I got dibs on that
newfangled revolver of his.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
You sure about this?
Well, if anything, it feels
good to be out here again,
in this era.
Well, don't get too attached.
That is what I keep telling myself.
I'll be drawing for Sheriff Palmer.
How do me and my boys know
you're going to keep your word?
Sheriff Palmer's a straight shooter.
Then he should be the one in the street.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[triumphant Western music]
Jefferson, are you all right?
Yeah.
Did you just shoot somebody for me?
Yeah. You're welcome.
I don't think we're done here yet.
[people shouting]
Oh, no.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
They found us.
[lasers whirring]
- [gunshot]
- Ah, friends! Welcome.
I think you'll find this slightly more
effective than your current sidearm.
Yes, I will be wanting
that back, by the way.
And you'll be needing this.
What about revealing our
future tech to the locals?
It doesn't seem to bother them. Shall we?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
What about our guns?
Sorry. Grabbed what I could.
That's what's up!
Y'all better stay the hell away from us!
Calm down, Jefferson.
- Traitor!
- Not possible.
I was never on your side. I was on my side.
- You'll never win!
- Wake up, pal. We already did.
Fool. The Time Masters have
initiated Omega Protocol.
The Pilgrim's coming for you, Chronos.
Your deaths are just a matter of time.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, that was easy.
♪ ♪
- You're not staying.
- Are you?
Me? You know I can't.
But this town still needs a sheriff.
Well, I'm not the
law-and-order type...
nor the staying-in-one-place
type either.
Well, we have that much in common at least.
At least.
Be well, Jonah.
Nice thing about my world...
for you, it ain't going anywhere.
Ah, perhaps we will see
each other again, my friend.
Yeah.
I reckon that'd be okay.
[clicks tongue]
Interesting fella.
Indeed.
This town's seen a lot of interesting.
Suppose you got one of those doohickies
that erases people's memories or something?
No. But...
skepticism and disbelief are
a far more effective tool.
Ah. So, if anybody here talks,
no one will believe them.
Would you, Mr. Snart?
[indistinct chatter]
I'm not going to pretend
to understand what I saw.
I'd prefer that you didn't
tell anyone about it either.
That goes for you too, young Master Neal.
- My last name's Wells.
- Excuse me?
His father's surname.
Herbert George Wells.
You're H.G. Wells.
H.G.... I like that.
Astonishing.
God, it feels so good to
be in normal clothes again.
The people here need to
invent fabric softener asap.
Is that all?
It's just that you've seemed a little off
ever since you came
back from your walkabout.
Ray, I told you...
Something, but I don't
think it's the whole truth.
I thought that we decided
to be honest with each other.
And I am.
I am being honest with you, Ray.
Look, I met a woman, and
I learned some things.
I told you about killing Savage.
And the rest...
the rest is what she
thought, not what I think.
I don't have to listen to her.
[sentimental music]
♪ ♪
I love you.
I love you too.
I think they're waiting
for us on the bridge.
We should go.
So how are you feeling, given your concerns
about becoming addicted
to this era once again?
[scoffs] The last time I left, Martin,
I did it to be with those closest to me.
I'm doing the same again.
So where to now?
Or, more specifically, when?
Is there another Fragmentation
we can hide out in?
Unfortunately, matters
are not quite so simple.
How'd I know you were gonna
say something like that?
- Rip's buddies.
- And yours.
The Time Masters have issued
Omega Protocols on all of us.
That sounds pretty terrible.
The worst kind of order they can issue...
they've sent the Pilgrim after us.
Who's the Pilgrim?
The Pilgrim is the Time
Masters' most deadly assassin,
and she will stop at nothing until
each and every one of you are dead.
Ooh, scary.
Pretty sure we can handle ourselves.
Indeed...
which is why she won't be going
after the present-day versions of you.
She's hunting our younger selves.
_
And she won't stop until
each and every one of us
has been erased from the timeline.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[laser fires]
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com